1aauto.com 2019-06-05

# 1A Auto Privacy Policy

**1A Auto, Inc.**

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy” or “Policy”) governs the manner in which 1A Auto, Inc. (“1A Auto,” “we,” “our,” “us” and similar terms) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users who register for and/or use this website (the “Website”). We take reasonable steps to protect user privacy consistent with the guidelines set forth in this Policy and with applicable U.S. state and federal laws. WE TAKE THESE PRECAUTIONS IN AN EFFORT TO PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION AGAINST SECURITY BREACHES. HOWEVER, THIS IS NOT A GUARANTEE THAT SUCH INFORMATION MAY NOT BE ACCESSED, DISCLOSED, ALTERED, OR DESTROYED BY BREACH OF SUCH FIREWALLS AND SECURE SERVER SOFTWARE. BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO ASSUME THESE RISKS. 

In this Policy, “user” or “you” means any individual using the Website. This Policy forms part of and is incorporated into our Terms of Use published at [https://www.1aauto.com/customer_service/terms_of_u...](https://www.1aauto.com/customer_service/terms_of_use) (the “Terms of Use”).  

BY ACCESSING OR USING THE WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, DO NOT USE THE WEBSITE. 

What Information Do We Collect? 

Limited Personal Information: We may collect certain personal information about you in connection with your use of the Website, including: (a) when you register to use the Website, we may collect the personal information through our online registration form, such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, vehicle information, username, password and other information detailed therein; (b) if you pay your fees by credit card, we (or a third-party payment processor acting on our behalf) will collect the name, expiration date and credit card number for the relevant card; and (c) if you communicate with us by email but do not otherwise register to use the Website, we will collect your email address. All of this information is referred to in this Policy as “Personal Information.” If you contact 1A Auto and disclose additional personal information, we may store that information. 

In order to access the online store section of the Website, rather than creating a 1A Auto account, you may register using your login credentials from your Facebook, Google or other social media account (your “Connected Account”). If you use a Connected Account, we may access and collect certain personal information (such as your name and email address) that your privacy settings on such Connected Account permit us to access. 

_User Data_. “User Data” means all data—other than Personal Information—that users provide us regarding or related to themselves or their use of or access to the Website. As described in the Terms of Use, we store User Data and correlate User Data with third-party data in order to make the Website available. 

_Web Tracking Information and Cookies_ : We and our Contractors (as defined below) may use web tracking technologies such as cookies, pixel tags and clear GIFs in order to operate the Website efficiently and to collect data related to usage of the Website. Such collected data (“Web Tracking Information”) may include the address of other websites you have visited, the type of browser you are using, device model, device ID and other unique device identifiers, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, what pages in the Website you visit and what links you clicked on, and whether you opened email communications we send to you. We and our Contractors may also use web tracking technologies that are placed in web pages on the Website or in email communications to collect information about actions that users take when they interact with the Website or such email communications. We do not correlate Web Tracking Information to individual user Personal Information. Some Web Tracking Information may include data, such as IP address data, that is unique to you. We use this information not to identify individual users, but to analyze trends, administer the Website, track users’ movements around the Website, and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole which provides us with the ability to determine aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns. 

A cookie is a small text file or record that is stored on a user’s computer when you visit our Website, which collects information about your activities on the Website. The cookies transmit this information back to the computers at 1A Auto or our third-party distributors of banners and newsletters; these computers are, generally speaking, the only computers which are authorized to read such information. The information captured makes it possible for us to: (i) speed navigation, and provide you with custom tailored content; (ii) remember information you give to us, so you don’t have to reenter it each time you visit the Website; (iii) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (iv) monitor total number of visitors, pages viewed, and the total number of banners served. You can choose to have your browser warn you every time a cookie is being sent to you or you can turn off cookie placement. Also, by not using cookies, your overall internet browsing experience will be affected. 

How Do We Use the Information We Collect? 

_Personal Information and User Data_ : We will use and store your Personal Information and User Data for the purpose of delivering the Website, and to analyze and enhance the operation of the Website. We may also use your Personal Information and User Data for the internal operational and administrative purposes of the Website. 

If you purchase products from our Website, we may use any Personal Information and User Data you provide to fulfill your order and for one-time and recurring billing purposes according to the terms pertaining to such order. If we (or our payment processor) have trouble processing an order, such information may be used to contact you. Payment card information is sent in encrypted format and is used only to send to our payment card processor, for the purposes of collecting payment for products ordered. We never make this information visible to anyone other than our payment card processor and never communicate it over a non-encrypted connection. The full payment card number is never seen by anyone inside our company, once entered and submitted, except by the payment card processor for the purposes of authorizing, clearing and reversing charges to your payment card. 

_Web Tracking Information_ : We use Web Tracking Information to administer the Website and to understand how well our Website is working, to store your user preferences, and to develop statistical information on usage of the Website. This allows us to determine which features visitors like best to help us improve the Website, to personalize your user experience, and to measure overall effectiveness. 

_Aggregate and De-Identified Information_ : We will also create statistical, aggregated and/or de-identified data relating to our users and the Website for analytical and commercial purposes. Aggregated and/or de-identified data is derived from Personal Information and User Data but in its aggregated and/or de-identified form, it does not duplicate or reveal any User Data or relate to or identify any individual. This data is used to understand our customer base and to develop, improve and market our services. 

_Customer Reviews_ : We may post to the Website and use for marketing purposes user reviews, testimonials and social media posts or comments about the Website or our products or services (collectively, “Reviews”), whether such Reviews are posted on our Website or on social media, and we may use Reviews in other formats consistent with consent received. Reviews may contain personally identifiable information. We may use your Personal Information to contact you to obtain a Review and obtain your consent via email or agreement sent via fax, pdf or mail prior to using such Review and/or using your name along with your Review. 

_Legal Exception_ : Notwithstanding the above, we may store and use Personal Information and User Data to the extent required by law or legal process, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements (including this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use) with you, or if in our reasonable discretion use is necessary to protect our legal rights or to protect third parties. 

_Promotional Communications_ : If you register and provide your email address, we may send you administrative and promotional emails. 

_Account Closure_ : If any of your account information appears to be incorrect, please contact us and let us know. If you close your account, we will delete any Personal Information associated with your account, but other information you submitted that is not associated with you personally may not be deleted. 

What Information Do We Disclose to Third Parties? 

_Personal Information and User Data_ : We will not disclose your Personal Information or User Data to any third parties except as follows: 

(i) To third-party contractors engaged to provide services on our behalf (“Contractors”), such as analyzing data and usage of the Website, hosting and operating the Website, soliciting customer reviews, providing marketing, payment processing or support and maintenance services for the Website, shipping products or providing customer service. We enter into agreements with all Contractors that require Contractors to use the Personal Information they receive only to perform services for us. 

(ii) When we have your consent to share the information. 

_Web Tracking Information_ : We disclose Web Tracking Information to Contractors, in order to analyze the performance of the Website and the behavior of users, and to operate and improve the Website. 

_Aggregate and De-Identified Information_ : We may disclose aggregated and/or de-identified data that does not contain Personal Information or User Data to any third parties, such as Contractors, potential customers, business partners, marketers, and funding sources, in order to describe our business and operations. 

_Network Operators_ : Use of the Website may involve use of the services of third-party telecommunications carriers. Such carriers are not our contractors, and any information that a carrier collects in connection with your use of the Website is not “Personal Information” and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the acts or omissions of telecommunications carriers. 

_Additional Disclosures_ : We reserve the right to disclose any information we collect in connection with the Website, including Personal Information, to: (a) any successor to our business as a result of any merger, acquisition, asset sale or similar transaction; and (b) any law enforcement, judicial authority, or governmental or regulatory authority, to the extent required by law or if in our reasonable discretion disclosure is necessary to enforce or protect our legal rights or to protect third parties. 

Privacy Settings/Opt Out 

If you would like your name and email address permanently removed from our database, please [email us](https://www.1aauto.com/about/contact). We will promptly delete your name and email address and you will no longer receive email from 1A Auto. Your removal from the mailing list or database will not remove data you have submitted to us or records of past use of the Website, nor delete information stored in our data backups and archives. Such data will be maintained and/or deleted in the ordinary course of 1A Auto’s business. 

If you wish to opt out of promotional emails (but would not like to have your information permanently removed from our database), you may do so by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in the email, or by contracting customer service via [email](https://www.1aauto.com/about/contact) or phone at (888) 844-3393. All users receive administrative emails, and so you cannot opt out of them while you remain registered. 

General 

_Security_ : We use reasonable security precautions to protect the security and integrity of your Personal Information in accordance with this Policy and applicable law. However, no Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that security breaches will not occur. Without limitation of the foregoing, we are not responsible for the actions of hackers and other unauthorized third parties that breach our reasonable security procedures. 

_Links_ : Our Website may contain links to other websites. 1A Auto is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those websites. Users should be aware of this when they leave our Website and review the privacy statements of each third-party website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Website. We encourage our users to read the privacy policies of these other websites before proceeding to use them. 

_Amendments_ : 1A Auto may modify or amend this Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes, as determined by 1A Auto, in the way in which Personal Information is collected, used or transferred, we will notify you of these changes by email. Notwithstanding any modifications we may make, any Personal Information collected by 1A Auto from you will be treated in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time information was collected, unless we obtain your consent otherwise. 

_Children_ : 1A Auto does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of the Website is directed at persons under 16. If you are under 16 years of age, then please do not use the Website. If 1A Auto learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 13 years of age has been collected without verifiable parental consent, then 1A Auto will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. To request the deletion of any such information, please [email us](https://www.1aauto.com/about/contact). 

Visitors from outside the United States: 1A Auto and its servers are located in the United States and are subject to the applicable state and federal laws of the United States. If you choose to access the Website, you consent to the use and disclosure of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and subject to such laws. 

Effective Date of this Policy: 11/28/18
